Gordon: This season on "MasterChef," we are making history...
戈登:本季 关于“MasterChef” 我们正在创造历史......
- Oh, my God! - ...because for the first time ever,
哦,我的上帝! - 因为对于 有史以来第一次,
we'll have partners in the kitchen.
我们将有合作伙伴 在厨房里。
Husbands and wives, mothers and daughters,
丈夫和妻子, 母亲和女儿,
- best friends, even divorced couples. - Give her a nice kiss.
最好的朋友, 离婚的夫妻。 给她一个漂亮的吻。
- This is "MasterChef: Dynamic Duos." - We're here, baby!
这是“MasterChef: 动态Duos 。 " 我们在这里,宝贝!
This season we will crown two MasterChefs.
这个赛季我们将加冕 两位大厨
- We have the best chemistry. - We are here to take the title.
我们有最好的化学。 我们在这里取标题。
- And who's in charge? - We fight over that a little bit, but--
谁负责? 我们为那个而战 一点点,但是——
- Me! - Joe and myself will be joined by a brand new judge...
- 我! 乔和我自己将加入 崭新的法官...
Tiffany Derry! Oh, yes!
蒂芙尼·德里! 哦,是的!
This competition is going to be fierce.
竞争 将会很凶猛。
...to find out if two cooks really are better than one.
找出两个厨师是否 真的比一个好。
They are like synchronized swimmers.
他们就像 同步游泳者。
- Come on. - The dynamic in this duo has disappeared.
- 来吧。 - 这中的动态 二人组消失了。
Was not my call, Chef. It was his call.
“不是我的电话,厨师。 那是他的电话。
You need you need to own your partner's decision.
你需要拥有 你的伴侣的决定。
I'm doing my best. Just calm down.
我尽力了。 只是冷静下来。
We are doubling the difficulty with new challenges...
我们正在加倍的困难 随着新的挑战...
This is only possible as a dynamic duo.
这只能是可能的 作为充满活力的二人组。
Ten minutes, ten minutes, ten minutes, ten minutes. Sold!
十分钟,十分钟, 十分钟,十分钟。 卖了!
We're gonna play recipe telephone.
我们要玩 食谱电话。
Me and Kayla are telepathic twins.
我和凯拉 心灵感应双胞胎。
Come on! Sauce!
来吧! 酱汁!
Time for the big swap. Are you ready?
大交换的时间。 你准备好了吗?
Cait, the sauce!
蔡,酱汁!
- Lift! - ...and some familiar favorites.
电梯! 和一些熟悉的 最喜欢的。
The return of the dreaded pressure test.
可怕的回归 压力测试。
- Get it, get it, get it. Where is it? - You grab it. Right there.
得到它,得到它,得到它。 它在哪里? 你抓住它。 就在那里。
- Wow, the wall. - We want identical plates.
哇,墙。 我们想要相同的盘子。
- Do you hear me? - I can't.
你听到我吗? 我可不能。
- Jess, two piece asparagus! - I can't hear you!
杰斯,两块芦笋! 我听不到你!
- ( whistle blowing ) - Oh, my God!
- (吹口哨) 哦,我的上帝!
It'll take all they've got to stay on track...
它会拿走他们所拥有的一切 保持正轨...
- We have to start plating! - We got an overcooked duck.
我们必须开始镀层! 我们得到了一只煮熟的鸭子。
- Oh, my God. - This is a freaking train wreck.
哦,我的上帝。 这是一个怪胎 火车残骸。
- Holy ( bleep ). - Whoo!
- 神圣的(bleep ) 。 - Whoo!
...and weather every storm.
和天气每一场风暴。
- This weather is crazy! - We're not ( bleep ) around.
这个天气太疯狂了! We're not ( bleep ) 。
- I want to get off this ride. - You're going home.
我想离开这个旅程。 你回家了。
- Oh, hey, medic! Medic! - ( wheezing )
哦,嘿,医生! 医学! (Wheezing)
But the duo that proves they're dynamic enough...
但证明的二人组 他们足够活跃......
- This is Michelin star chef's plating. - Yes!
这是米其林星级 厨师的电镀。 - 是的!
- This is explosive. - Thank you so much.
这是爆炸性的。 谢谢你这么多。
I really see the dynamic duo.
我真的看到了充满活力的二人组。
You've got the marriage right here. A bit like you two.
你有 婚姻就在这里。 有点像你们两个。
...will share the ultimate culinary prize.
分享终极 烹饪奖。
- Together you're cooking like pros. - Oh, my God.
在一起 you're 像专业人士一样烹饪。 哦,我的上帝。
- As a duo, this is the level you need to be at. - Thank you, Chef.
作为二人组,这是水平 你需要在。 谢谢你,厨师。
- This is better than some of my restaurants. - Oh, Joe!
这比一些好。 我的餐馆。 哦,乔!
You may kiss the bride.
你可以亲吻新娘。
This is "MasterChef: Dynamic Duos."
这是“主厨: 动态Duos 。 "
I don't like cooking without you.
我不喜欢做饭 没有你。
( cheering )
(欢呼)
MasterChef! Here we are!
主厨! 我们来了!
- There it is! There it is! - Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
那里! 是! “是的,先生。 是的,先生。
Let's go!
我们走吧!
Oh, my gosh.
哦,天哪。
- Oh, wow. - It's so pretty.
哦,哇。 太漂亮了。
- We're here! Can you believe it? - I can't believe it.
我们在这里! 你能相信吗? 我不敢相信。
- Let's go! - Come on!
我们走吧! 来吧!
- We're here. - Oh, my God!
我们在这里。 哦,我的上帝!
- I feel so emotional. Can you believe it? - I know.
我感到如此情绪化。 你能相信吗? 我知道。
We love cooking together. So when we found out that this season
我们喜欢一起做饭。 所以当我们发现 这个季节
- we're gonna be together... - It was like the dream come true for us.
我们会在一起的...... 就像梦一样 为我们成真。
I can't believe that we're here.
我不敢相信 我们在这里。
This is my partner in life and in the kitchen.
这是我生活中的伴侣 在厨房里。
- This is what we've been training for. - We're cooking all off.
- 这就是什么 我们一直在训练。 我们做饭了。
And this is what we want to do for the rest of our lives.
这就是我们想要做的 在我们的余生里。
- Dude, I'm just happy to be here doing this with you. - This is gonna be awesome.
Dude, I'm just happy to 哥德,我只是很高兴 在这里和你做这个。 这将是伟大的。
- Yeah, man. You, too. - Inside those doors is our dream.
是的,伙计。 你,也是。 那些门里面 这是我们的梦想。
- Mm-hmm. - I'm like, where's Gordon?
- 嗯。 我就像,戈登在哪里?
- ( shrieking ) - Whoa.
( 尖叫 ) - 呃。
Gordon: Let's go.
戈登:我们走吧。
( screaming, cheering )
(尖叫,欢呼)
- ( cheering continues ) - Gordon: I'm excited.
- (继续欢呼) 戈登:我很兴奋。
Oh, my goodness me.
哦,我的天哪。
Welcome, everybody,
欢迎大家,
to our incredible 15th season of "MasterChef."
令人难以置信的第15季 “主厨”
- Yeah! - ( cheering )
- 是的! - ( 欢呼)
- Oh, my God. - But listen up.
哦,我的上帝。 但是听着。
"MasterChef" has always been about finding
“主厨”一直 关于寻找
- America's best home cook. - Oh, yeah.
美国最好的家庭厨师。 哦,是的。
But this year we want to highlight the power of partners in the kitchen.
但今年我们要 突出合作伙伴的力量 在厨房里。
For the first time in "MasterChef" history,
第一次 在“主厨”的历史中,
we will crown not one, but two MasterChefs.
我们不要冠冕, 两位大厨。
- How cool is that? - Baby, right here!
这有多酷? 宝贝,就在这里!
This is "MasterChef: Dynamic Duos."
这是“主厨: 动态Duos 。 "
( cheering )
(欢呼)
- Yes! Yes! Yes! - Whoo!
- 是的! 是的! 是的! - Whoo!
We have brought the best duos from all across America
我们带来了最好的二人组 来自全美各地
here to the amazing MasterChef kitchen.
这里 惊人 MasterChef厨房。
And trust me, we have everything from husbands and wives.
相信我, 我们有一切 丈夫和妻子。
- Yeah! - To mothers and daughters,
是啊! - 给母亲和女儿,
- aunts and nieces. Yes? - Yeah!
阿姨和侄女。 是的? 是啊!
Best friends.
最好的朋友。
- Even co-workers. - Whoo!
甚至同事。 - Whoo!
Amazing!
惊人!
We even have a divorced couple?
我们甚至有 离婚的夫妻?
- Happily! Happily! - Amazing.
幸福! 快乐! - 惊人。
Look at the distance between you two still.
看看远方 两个人之间还在。
- Closer together. - Give a nice kiss.
更近了。 给一个漂亮的吻。
It's gonna be interesting watching you two cook.
会很有意思 看着你两个做饭。
And, young lady, you are hyperventilating-- in the yellow, yes?
年轻女士, 你过度通风—— 黄色,是吗?
- Yes, that's right. - Why now?
是的,这是正确的。 为什么是现在?
We've said forever that that once there was a partner season
我们永远说过这一点 曾经有一个合作伙伴的季节
that we would be there. So here we are.
我们会在那里。 所以我们在这里。
Glad to hear it. And who's in charge?
很高兴听到它。 谁负责?
- We fight over that a little bit. - Me, me!
我们为那个而战 一点点。 我,我!
- Wow. - Well, here's the thing, guys,
- 哇。 好了,事情是这样的,伙计们,
even though you're competing as a duo, we're not going to be judging as a duo.
即使你竞争 作为二人组,我们不会去 判断为二人组。
This season we'll be joined by a new judge.
这个赛季我们将加入 新法官
- Wow. - Ooh!
- 哇。 - 哦!
Someone that is no stranger to the MasterChef kitchen.
并不陌生的人 主厨厨房
- She... - Oh, it's a woman!
她...... 哦,是女人!
...is a decorated chef with nearly 30 years of culinary experience.
. . . 是装饰厨师 近30年 烹饪经验。
Oh, my God. Who's that?
哦,我的上帝。 是谁?
And like us, she has her own culinary empire.
和我们一样,她有自己的 烹饪帝国。
- Now, are you ready to meet her? - Yes!
现在,你准备好了吗 遇见她? - 是的!
- Here she comes. - Oh!
她来了。 - 哦!
( chattering, cheering )
(喋喋不休,欢呼)
Wow!
哇!
Oh, my God.
哦,我的上帝。
- Who's it gonna be? - Please give a warm welcome
谁会是? - 请热烈欢迎
to the amazing...
到惊人的...
- Tiffany Derry! - ( cheering )
蒂芙尼·德里! - (欢呼)
Tiffany is an incredible, world-renowned, award-winning chef,
蒂芙尼是一个不可思议的人, 世界知名, 获奖厨师,
a celebrated restaurateur,
一个著名的餐馆老板,
and a true culinary icon of the South.
一个真正的烹饪偶像 南方。
We are so lucky to have her join the MasterChef family.
我们很幸运有她。 加入MasterChef家族。
- Oh, man! Good to see you, darling. - How are you?
哦,伙计! 很高兴见到你,亲爱的。 你怎么样?
- Welcome. - Oh, my God!
- 欢迎。 哦,我的上帝!
Wow. How cool is this to have Tiffany Derry as our new judge?
哇。 这是多么酷 蒂芙尼·德里作为我们的新法官?
- Come on, give it up. - Yeah!
来吧,放弃它。 是啊!
- ( cheering ) - Yeah!
- ( 欢呼) 是啊!
- Tiffany, welcome to the MasterChef family. - Thank you.
- 蒂芙尼,欢迎 给MasterChef家族。 - 谢谢。
What a pleasure and an honor to have you here.
多么快乐和荣誉 让你在这里。
Now tell us a little bit how you worked your way
现在告诉我们一点点 你的工作方式
through the culinary ranks.
通过烹饪行列。
Give us an insight to the beginning of that journey.
给我们一个洞察 这段旅程的开始。
I started as a server. At 16, I was managing.
我开始作为一个服务器。 16岁时,我在管理。
And now to be able to own your own,
现在能够 拥有自己的,
I think is one of the most beautiful things about spreading love and great food.
我认为是其中最多的一个 关于传播的美好事物 爱和伟大的食物。
- Love that. Love that! - ( cheering )
爱这个。 爱这个! - (欢呼)
Right. On to the reason why you're all here.
对。 关于原因 为什么你们都在这里。
Listen up because at the end of this competition,
听,因为在最后 竞争,
the best duo will earn the title, the trophy,
最好的二人组将赚取 冠军,奖杯,
and a quarter of a million dollars.
四分之一 一百万元。
Right here! You've got the winners right here.
就在这里! 你有赢家 就在这里。
But you may think that competing as duos could be easier.
但你可能会认为竞争 作为二人组可以更容易。
But trust me, this season is gonna be twice as tough.
相信我,这个季节 这将是两倍的艰难。
Because tonight, to earn your spot in the competition,
因为今晚,为了赚钱 你在比赛中的位置,
you'll face off in a battle against another duo.
你会在战斗中对峙 反对另一个二人组。
- Ooh. - It's a battle you need to win
- 哦。 这是一场你需要赢的战斗
to get your hands on two of these.
得到你的手 其中两个。
- Woohoo! - That's right.
- Woohoo ! - 没错。
The incredible MasterChef apron.
不可思议的主厨围裙。
- Whoo! - Yeah!
- Whoo! 是啊!
My name on it.
我的名字。
In these audition battles, two duos will enter the MasterChef kitchen,
在这些试镜战斗中, 两个人将进入 MasterChef厨房,
- but only one duo will leave with aprons. - Oh.
只有一个二人组 会带着围裙离开。 - 哦。
And you're gonna have just 30 minutes on the clock.
And you're gonna have 你 时钟上只有30分钟。
- Oh, man. - Gordon: Right.
哦,伙计。 戈登:对。
it's time for our first duos to battle it out
是时候为我们的第一双 战斗出来
to get their hands on that coveted MasterChef apron.
得到他们的手 令人垂涎的MasterChef围裙。
All of you, the very best of luck.
所有人, 运气最好的。
- We'll see you in the kitchen. - Thank you.
我们会在厨房里见到你。 - 谢谢。
( music playing )
(音乐演奏)
Wow, this is gonna be so exciting.
哇,这将是 如此令人兴奋。
- I cannot wait to cook. - Oh, my God.
我等不及要做饭了。 哦,我的上帝。
- I need my apron, Javier. - Ah!
我需要我的围裙,哈维尔。 啊!
- If you don't give me my apron, Javier-- - Yes. No, no, no.
如果你不给我 我的围裙,哈维尔—— - 是的。 不,不,不。
- You got it. Don't worry. - Half of us are getting an apron.
你得到了它。 别担心。 我们的一半是 得到一个围裙。
- That's insane. - Gordon on PA: Right.
这太疯狂了。 戈登在PA:对。
First up, Jesse and Jessica...
先上, 杰西和杰西卡
- Oh! - Oh!
- 哦! - 哦!
...versus Michelle and Zach.
反对 米歇尔和扎克。
( cheering )
(欢呼)
J-Squared!
Oh, my God.
哦,我的上帝。
- Oh, my God! - Jesse: We don't want to live
哦,我的上帝! 杰西:我们不想活下去
that straightforward 9 to 5 life anymore.
直截了当 9到5个生命
Once we get the apron, we're not looking back.
一旦我们得到围裙, 我们不是回头看。
We are here to be the next MasterChefs.
我们在这里是为了 下一个MasterChefs
- Come on down. Come on down. - Hi!
下来吧。 下来。 - 你好!
Now tell us who you are and what the relationship is between this dynamic duo.
现在告诉我们你是谁 以及什么关系 在这个动态的二人组之间。
I'm Zach. This is Michelle.
我是扎克。 这是米歇尔。
We're from Minneapolis, Minnesota.
我们来自明尼阿波利斯, 明尼苏达州。
- We've been married for four years. - Yeah.
我们结婚了 四年。 - 是的。
- Watching "MasterChef" for 15. - Yes.
观看“MasterChef”为15。 - 是的。
Big, big, big fans of "MasterChef."
大,大,大粉丝 “主厨”。
It essentially brought us together
它本质上 把我们聚集在一起
and probably why we're married today.
和可能 我们今天为什么结婚。
- Love that. - And?
爱这个。 和?
We're J-Squared. My name is Jesse.
我们是J-Squared。 我的名字叫杰西。
This is my beautiful partner Jessica.
这是我的美丽 伙伴杰西卡。
- And we are New England foodies. - Nice.
And we are 我们 新英格兰美食家 - 尼斯。
Okay, you are now fighting for a spot
好吧,你现在 争取一个地点
in the MasterChef kitchen, guys.
在MasterChef厨房,伙计们。
- We're ready. Yeah. - Let's go.
我们准备好了。 是的。 我们走吧。
Okay, your 30 minutes starts now.
好的,你的30分钟 现在开始。
- Whoo! - Let's go.
- Whoo! 我们走吧。
- Let's go, baby. - All right. Ingredients.
走吧,宝贝。 没事。 成分。
- All right, we're heating oil. - Yup.
好了,我们在加热油。 - 是的。
- Doing it baby. We're doing it. - We're doing this.
做它宝贝。 我们在做。 我们正在做这个。
What are we looking for in this season of duos?
我们看什么 在这个季节的二重奏中?
I'm looking for the bond. I'm looking for the trust.
我正在寻找债券。 我在寻找信任。
And more importantly, communication, right?
更重要的是, 沟通,对吧?
- I love you. - I love you, too.
我爱你。 我爱你,也是。
- Two tablespoons of sugar, babe? Two tablespoons sugar? - Yes. Yep.
两汤匙糖, 宝贝? 两汤匙糖? - 是的。 是的。
But also what they put on the plate should be exceptional because it's two phenomenal
但也放什么 盘子应该是例外的 因为它是两个惊人的
- amateur chefs coming in as one. - Yeah.
- 业余厨师 进来如一。 是啊。
All right, let's go. We got to get going on the chicken.
没事,我们走吧。 我们得走了 在鸡身上。
- Let's go. - Zach and Michelle.
我们走吧。 Zach 和 Michelle 。
Give us an insight to the dish, please.
给我们一个见解 盘子,请。
Yeah, this is a chili spice
是的,这是一种辣椒香料
chicken leg quarter on top of a parmesan
鸡腿季度 在 parmesan 的顶端
- mascarpone polenta. - Love that.
- 睫毛膏。 爱这个。
And is this a dish you would cook for a dinner party?
这是你会做的一道菜吗? 做饭参加晚宴?
We've got a one-year-old at home, so the dinner parties
我们有一个一岁的孩子 在家里,所以晚宴
have kind of taken a little bit of a dip lately.
有某种采取 最近有点蘸。
- Congrats. How'd you meet? - We were friends first. Met through a friend group.
- 恭喜。 你是怎么认识的? 我们首先是朋友。 通过朋友群见面。
And eventually we realized, "Wait a second. I think I love you."
最终 我们意识到,“等一等。 我想我爱你 。 "
- "I think I love you, too." - Gordon: You think?
“我想我也爱你。 戈登:你觉得呢?
- Really? Yeah. - Love that.
真的吗? 是的。 爱这个。
So we're coming up to 10 minutes down with 20 minutes to go.
所以我们要来了 10分钟下来 走了20分钟。
- Whoo! - Jessica and Jesse, what are you cooking?
- Whoo! 杰西卡和杰西, 你在煮什么?
A crispy skin salmon served with an aji verde Peruvian green sauce and pickled fresnos.
香脆的皮肤鲑鱼 aji verde 秘鲁绿色 酱汁和腌制的 brenos 。
- Oh, love that idea. - Wow!
哦,喜欢这个想法。 哇!
- Yeah! - Love that. How'd you guys meet?
是啊! 爱这个。 你们是怎么认识的?
We actually used to bartend next to each other in Boston.
我们实际上习惯了调酒 在波士顿的彼此。
And there was a lot of dancing around each other,
还有很多 互相跳舞,
and then that dancing ended up progressing,
然后跳舞 最终进步,
- and here we are eight years later. - Wow.
- 在这里,我们是 八年后。 - 哇。
Nice. Looks good, looks good.
尼斯。 看起来不错,看起来不错。
- Nice, nice. All right. - So, Zack and Michelle's chicken,
很好,很好。 好的。 扎克和米歇尔的 鸡,
- it sounds delicious. - Yeah, yeah.
听起来很美味。 是的,是的。
Especially that lovely creamy polenta.
尤其是那 可爱的奶油蛋黄酱。
Also I love seeing the chicken thigh and--
我也喜欢看 鸡大腿和——
- It's what I was about to say. - Yeah.
那就是我要说的。 - 是的。
Is there jeopardy in a half hour of properly cooking
半小时内有危险吗? 正确烹饪
- a complete chicken leg and thigh? - There's-- yeah. Absolutely.
- 一个完整的 鸡腿和大腿? 有——是的。 绝对。
- Yeah, you got your work cut out there. - Mm-hmm.
是的,你有你的工作 剪下来。 - 嗯。
- All right oven open. - Yep. Chicken going in.
- 打开所有正确的烤箱。 - 是的。 鸡进去了。
- Yep. It's going in. All right. - Love it.
- 是的。 进去了。 没事。 爱它。
Beautiful.
美丽。
- You make this in your sleep. - Yep. Nice.
你在睡梦中做这个。 - 是的。 尼斯。
The salmon dish with Jesse and Jessica, it sounds intriguing.
鲑鱼盘 杰西和杰西卡, 听起来很有趣。
Yeah, it sounds punchy, flavorful.
是的, 听起来很刺耳,有味道。
- I like the Peruvian accents. - And I love a crispy skin.
我喜欢秘鲁口音。 我喜欢香脆的皮肤。
Any. I mean, salmon, love to see that technique.
任何。 我的意思是,鲑鱼, 喜欢看这个技术。
But the technique about searing the salmon is very, very important.
但技术关于 灼热鲑鱼是非常的, 非常重要。
- So they're kind of pushing it. - How does the skin look, baby?
所以他们有点推它。 皮肤看起来怎么样,宝贝?
- Tell me how it feels. - Yeah, that feels crispy.
告诉我感觉如何。 是的,那感觉脆。
- Okay, yep. - Looking good, looking good.
好的,是的。 看起来不错,看起来不错。
- Thanks. - Tell me what you think and taste the seasoning.
- 谢谢。 告诉我你怎么想 品尝调味料。
Both couples are non-stop talking, communicating, tasting.
两对夫妻都是不停歇的 交谈,交流,品尝。
- Yes. - Needs a little salt, I think.
- 是的。 需要一点盐,我想。
- Needs a little salt? - Yep.
需要一点盐吗? - 是的。
- 15 minutes gone. 15 minutes remaining. - Whoa.
15分钟过去了。 剩下15分钟。 - 嘌嘌。
Remember only two aprons up for grabs for one dynamic duo.
记住两个围裙 抓住一个动态的二人组。
You do not want to go home empty-handed.
你不想回家 空手。
- Heard. - Heard.
- 听到。 - 听到。
- Let's go. - Need to get that sauce going, babycakes.
我们走吧。 需要让酱汁去, 婴儿蛋糕。
- Yep. I'm almost there. - Ooh, babycakes.
- 是的。 我差不多在那里。 哦,宝贝蛋糕。
- Say nice things like that to me. - You got it, babycakes.
说好的东西 像这样对我来说。 你得到了它,宝贝蛋糕。
Where's that meat thermometer? Where's that meat thermometer?
肉温度计在哪里? 肉温度计在哪里?
- Jessica, Jesse! J-Squared! - Jesse: How are you?
杰西卡,杰西! J-Squared! 杰西:你怎么样?
- How we doing? - How much longer?
我们如何做? 多久?
Give it quick little temp, but I think we're looking pretty good.
给它快速的小温度, 但我认为我们在看 相当不错。
- What did you season it with? - Salt and pepper.
你用什么季节了? 盐和胡椒粉。
Heavy on the salt and pepper. Baby, want to feel this for me?
重在盐和胡椒粉上。 宝贝,想给我感受这些吗?
- Yep. - Feel good.
- 是的。 感觉很好。
- You know what I love about you guys working? - It feels great.
你知道我爱什么 关于你们工作? 感觉很棒。
Everything, y'all double check with each other.
一切,你们都双重检查 彼此。
- Jesse: Yes, yes. - Absolutely.
杰西:是的,是的。 - 绝对。
- Like a true team. - Yes, yes.
就像一个真正的团队。 是的,是的。
I seen you force fed him some broccolini.
看见你喂他 一些西兰花。
I force feed him all the time. All the time.
我强迫他所有的时间。 所有的时间。
- Right? - You know what to do. You opened up.
- 对吧? 你知道该怎么做。 你打开了。
Yeah, yeah, yeah. It's natural, right?
是的,是的。 这是自然的,对吧?
To sit here and go through that? It's awesome.
坐在这里 并通过这个? 真棒。
Y'all looking good. Good job y'all.
你们看起来都不错。 好工作你们所有人。
- Jessica: Beautiful. Thank you. - Hot open, hot open.
- 杰西卡: 美丽。 谢谢你。 热开,热开。
How we feeling about those tomatoes?
我们的感受 关于这些西红柿?
- Are they a little over? - No.
他们有点过吗? - 没有。
I am concerned about this polenta.
我很担心 关于这个polonta。
The water's not boiling yet. The stock's not boiling.
水还没有沸腾。 股票没有沸腾。
- Gordon: No. - Come on, polenta. Come on.
- 戈登:没有。 来吧,polonta。 来吧。
Michelle, is that polenta on?
米歇尔,那是在吗?
- It's not on yet. About to do that right now. - Please.
- 还没有。 马上要这样做。 - 请。
- I got it. I got it. - Please, please, please.
我得到了它。 我得到了。 请,请,请。
I would throw the polenta on in the beginning
我会把旗杆扔出去 在开始
- because waiting is not gonna make it any better. - No.
因为等待不是 会让它变得更好。 - 没有。
- ( sighs ) - What's up?
- (叹息) 怎么了?
The polenta. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
的polonta。 我们走吧。 我们走吧。 我们走吧。 我们走吧。
- Get it going! - They're nervous.
让它去! 他们很紧张。
- They're nervous for us? - Where's the polenta?
他们为我们紧张吗? 咔唫塔在哪里?
We just need to say some prayers.
我们只需要 说一些祈祷。
Damn. It's gonna be hard to get flavor there now.
该死的。 会很难的 现在在那里品尝风味。
I hope it's boiling.
我希望它是沸腾的。
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
走吧,我们走吧,我们走吧。
Come on.
来吧。
- All right, we're almost boiling here. - Michelle: Okay.
好的, 我们几乎在这里沸腾。 米歇尔:好的。
- Get it going. - I'm gonna need you for a taste.
让它去。 I'm gonna need you 我将需要你 品尝。
- Polenta going in. - Okay. Polenta in.
- 波伦塔进去。 - 好的。 波伦塔在。
- Lime... salt. - ( bleep ) delicious.
- 石灰...盐。 - ( bleep )美味。
- Is it? - It's so good. It's so good.
是吗? - 太好了。 真是好。
Oh, that's so good.
哦,那很好。
Whew! All right, there we go.
呜呜! 没事,我们去了。
10 minutes remaining. Right, how's that chicken, please?
剩下10分钟。 正确的, 请问这只鸡怎么样?
- It's gonna be great. - Yeah? Crank up the oven, okay?
会很棒。 是啊? 把烤箱放好,好吗?
- Make sure they're on. - 450, 450.
确保他们上。 - 450,450。
How come that polenta went on late?
怎么样,那个 polnta 迟到了?
- I know. Time flies. - What are you doing time?
- 我知道。 时间飞逝。 你在做什么时间?
- Congratulations on that baby, by the way. - Thank you so much.
- 祝贺 宝宝,顺便说一句。 谢谢你这么多。
Normally someone's at home always looking after,
通常有人在家 总是看着,
but both of you being here this far away,
你在这里 都在这里 如此遥远,
- how're you coping? - It's been hard. Yeah. You know?
你如何应对? - 很难。 是的。 你知道吗?
We're not gonna lie about that. But he's well cared for,
我们不会撒谎的。 但他被照顾得很好,
and we're showing him that you got to chase your dreams
我们向他展示这一点 你必须追逐你的梦想
- and this is what we're doing. - Good.
这就是我们正在做的事情。 - 很好。
Make sure that chicken's good. Get flavor in that polenta.
确保鸡的好。 在那个蛋黄酱里调味。
- We will. Yep. You got it. Thank you. - Good luck.
我们会的。 是的。 你得到了。 谢谢你。 祝你好运。
- Looks great. - Beautiful. Nice and crispy.
看起来很棒。 - 美丽。 漂亮和香脆。
- All right, chicken. - Looks good.
好的,鸡肉。 看起来不错。
- All right, let's go! - How do you feel?
走吧,我们走吧! 你感觉如何?
- Good? That good? - That's the sauce, babe.
很好? 很好? 那是酱汁,宝贝。
Two minutes to go. Start plating.
两分钟就走了。 开始电镀。
Here we go. This is all happening right now.
我们走。 这一切都在发生。
Get in there. Pour it on there. Pour it on there. Come on.
进去吧。 把它倒在那里。 把它倒在那里。 来吧。
Come on, guys. Finishing touches now. Come on.
来吧,伙计们。 现在完成触摸。 来吧。
Yeah, this is gonna be the prettiest part.
是的,这将是 最漂亮的部分。
- Looking delicious, babe. - Thanks.
看起来很好吃,宝贝。 - 谢谢。
- Come on. This little chunk. - Oh.
- 来吧。 这个小块。 - 哦。
- Woohoo-hoo-hoo! - Five, four, three, two, one.
Woohoo-hoo-hoo! - 五,四,三,二,一。
- And stop. Hands in the air. - High-five, high-five.
停止。 手在空中。 - 高五,高五。
- ( squeals ) - Gordon: Well done.
- ( 尖叫 ) 戈登:干得好。
Okay, Zach and Michelle, please present your dish.
好吧,扎克和米歇尔, 请出示你的菜。
Michelle: We have for you a chili-spiced chicken leg quarter
米歇尔:我们为你 辣椒香料鸡腿季度
on top of creamy mascarpone parmesan polenta,
在奶油睫毛膏的顶部 parmesan polenta,
blistered tomatoes, and topped with an anchovy breadcrumb.
水泡西红柿,和顶部 凤尾鱼面包屑。
It looks beautiful. I love the color on the chicken.
看起来很美。 我喜欢鸡的颜色。
I was nervous, the fact that it wasn't gonna be cooked in time,
我很紧张, 事实,它不是 会及时煮熟,
but you've proved me wrong there.
但你已经证明了我 错了。
Polenta still not on with 10 minutes to go,
波伦塔仍然没有 十分钟就走,
that's that's quite a scary area, but it looks so inviting.
那是相当可怕的 面积,但看起来如此诱人。
- Really well done. - Thank you.
真的很好做。 - 谢谢。
How long was the chicken in there for?
鸡有多长 进去是为了?
About 20 minutes?
大约20分钟?
Gordon: Chicken is cooked beautifully.
戈登: 鸡肉煮得很漂亮。
Tiffany: When Gordon was cutting into the chicken,
蒂芙尼: 当戈登切割时 进入鸡,
there was a moment where my mouth watered.
有一种时刻 我的嘴浇水的地方。
I said, "Ooh, that chicken look juicy!"
我说道, “哦,这只鸡看起来很多汁!”
- That chicken is delicious. - Aah!
这只鸡很好吃。 啊!
Gosh, you got the flavor on that chicken,
天哪,你得到了味道 在这只鸡身上,
and you did it in such a small amount of time.
你这样做在这样的 少量的时间。
- Thank you. - Thank you, Chef. Thank you.
- 谢谢。 谢谢你,大厨。 谢谢你。
The polenta's creamy. Beautifully seasoned.
蛋黄酱的奶油。 美丽的调味。
- Really good job. - Thank you. Thank you, Chef.
真的很好的工作。 谢谢你。 谢谢你,大厨。
Chicken is juicy. Maybe almost too juicy somehow.
鸡肉是多汁的。 也许几乎太多汁了。
- What? Never! - A word no one has ever said.
- 什么? 从来没有! 一句话从来没有人说过。
- I'll take it. - Yeah, we'll take that.
我会接受的。 是的,我们会接受的。
But an excellent-- an excellent dish.
但一个优秀的—— 极好的菜。
- Thank you. - Thank you, Joe.
- 谢谢。 谢谢你,乔。
Good job, guys.
好工作,伙计们。
- Well, we did good. - Yeah.
好吧,我们做得很好。 - 是的。
The double J, Jessica and Jesse.
双J, 杰西卡和杰西。
- J-Squared! - J-Squared!
J-Squared! J-Squared!
Jesse: What you have in front of you tonight
杰西:你有什么 今晚在你面前
is a crispy skin salmon with roasted broccolini
酥脆的皮肤鲑鱼 烤花椰菜
served with the aji verde Peruvian green sauce and some pickled fresnos.
与 Aji verde 合作 秘鲁绿酱 和一些腌制的Fresnos。
It's rare to have the courage to not put carbs or starches
有勇气是罕见的 不要放碳水化合物或淀粉
on a plate because you have nothing to fall back on,
在盘子里,因为你有 没有什么可以依靠的,
and it's really about the technique and the flavors.
这真的是关于 技术和口味。
Aside from that, it looks perfect.
除此之外, 看起来很完美。
- Thank you. - Thank you
谢谢你。 - 谢谢
Jesse, the temperature on the salmon, what were you looking for?
杰西,温度 在鲑鱼上,什么是 你在寻找?
We're looking for a little bit of medium rare inside of there.
我们正在寻找 一点点中等稀有 在里面。
Mm. It's pink. It looks beautiful.
姆。 是粉红色的。 看起来很美。
- The dish tastes as good as it looks. Exceptional. - Thank you.
- 菜品味道一样好 看起来。 例外。 谢谢你。
What I love here is you got that powerful umami bomb underneath
我爱这里的是,你得到了 强大的 umami 炸弹
- that just tantalizes the palate. Well done. - Thank you.
- 这只是诱人 口感。 干得好。 - 谢谢。
The salmon itself is unbelievable.
鲑鱼本身 难以置信。
I do think you could have seared it just a little bit longer.
我认为你可以烫伤 它只是稍微长一点。
But, I mean, gosh, it is-- it's good.
但是,我的意思是,天哪, 这是 - 这是好的。
- Thank you. - Thank you. Thank you so much.
谢谢你。 谢谢你。 谢谢你这么多。
The dish has great points of acidity.
这道菜有很大的分 酸度。
The broccolini is crunchy and soft at the same time. Excellent dish.
花椰菜是松脆的 柔软的同时。 优秀的菜肴。
- Both: Thank you. - Thank you.
两位:谢谢。 - 谢谢。
Appreciate it.
欣赏它。
Now we're faced with the toughest decision
现在我们面对 最艰难的决定
because nobody deserves to fly home.
因为没有人值得 飞回家。
- Excuse us. - Whew. Good job.
对不起。 - 呃。 好工作。
- Zach and Michelle's chicken. - Joe: Well-executed.
Zach和Michelle的鸡。 乔:执行得很好。
- Well-thought out dish. - Yeah.
- 深思熟虑的菜肴。 - 是的。
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
我感觉像 我要扔了。
The JJ salmon dish was also really good.
JJ 鲑鱼盘 也真的很好。
Halfway through that tasting across both dishes,
那次品尝的一半 跨越两个盘子,
I had to remind myself they're amateurs.
我不得不提醒自己 他们业余爱好者。
We're talking to them like pros.
我们像专业人士一样和他们交谈。
- We did everything in our power. - I know. I know.
我们做了一切 在我们的力量。 我知道。 我知道。
So we're in agreement then?
所以我们同意吗?
- Yeah. - Good.
- 是的。 - 很好。
( sighs )
(叹息)
All four of you really showed us the love tonight.
这四个人真的 今晚向我们展示了爱。
But one of these duos just edged out the others.
但是其中一个二人组 只是把其他人挤出来。
These aprons go to...
这些围裙去...
One of these duos just edged out the others.
其中一对 只是把其他人挤出来。
These aprons go to...
这些围裙去...
( indistinct chatter )
(indistinct chatter)
- Ah! - Here we go, here we go, here we go.
- 啊! 我们走,我们走, 我们走。
- ( gasping ) - ( screaming )
- ( 喘气 ) ( scream)
Yes! Yes!
是的! 是的!
( screaming )
(尖叫)
Michelle: It's hard to be here away from our son,
米歇尔:很难 远离我们的儿子,
but he's gonna be so proud of us.
但他将会 为我们感到骄傲。
He's gonna see that he can do anything that he wants,
他会看到他能做的 他想要的任何东西,
he can chase his dreams, because he saw us do it.
他可以追逐他的梦想, 因为他看见我们这样做。
And it means so much to us to be here, to be together.
意思是这么多 我们在这里, 在一起。
It's just a dream come true. We're so lucky to be here.
这只是梦想成真。 我们很幸运能来到这里。
- Love you. - Love you, too.
爱你。 爱你,也是。
Jessica: We want this so badly.
杰西卡: 我们想要这个如此糟糕。
So to have that snatched away from us was absolutely devastating.
所以要拥有它 被抢走离我们 绝对是毁灭性的。
We feel disappointed, not in our cook, by any means. Just the results.
我们感到失望, 而不是我们的厨师,无论如何。 只是结果。
Jessica: We did everything that we possibly could.
杰西卡:我们做了一切 我们可能。
I just hate losing talent like that. I hate it.
我只是讨厌 失去这样的天赋。 我讨厌它。
To send somebody home that cooked like that?
送人回家 那样煮的?
- Oh, my goodness me. That was tough. - ( Joe groans )
哦,我的天哪。 那是很艰难的。 (Joe 呻吟)
Gordon on PA: Right.
戈登在PA:对。
Next up, Aivan and Tina...
接下来,艾文和蒂娜...
Hello!
你好!
...versus Asa and Shanda.
阿萨和尚达。
Oh, yeah! Let's go, baby!
哦,是的! 走吧,宝贝!
- Let's go, baby! - Aivan: I'm so excited
走吧,宝贝! 艾凡:我太兴奋了
to showcase our culture, heritage,
展示我们的文化, 遗产,
flavors to the judges.
给评委们的口味。
And, Gordon, you better give me an apron
而且,戈登, 你最好给我一个围裙
- because I'm here for it! - She's gonna come take it.
因为我在这里! 她要来拿。
- Oh, my God. Yay! - Welcome.
哦,我的上帝。 耶! - 欢迎。
Shanda: Not getting an apron? Not an option.
尚达: 没有围裙吗? 不是一个选项。
We came here to compete. We came here to win.
我们来这里是为了竞争。 我们来这里是为了赢。
We got our entire family on our back.
我们得到了我们的整个家庭 在我们的背上。
So it's a lot of pressure, but we're here to do it.
所以压力很大, 但我们在这里是为了做这件事。
- Hello, hello! - I love it.
你好,你好! 我爱它。
All right, tell us who you are.
没事, 告诉我们你是谁。
- Introduce yourself. - I'm Tina. I'm 63 years old.
自我介绍。 我是Tina。 我63岁了。
I'm a retired fishing boat owner and this is my niece.
我是一个退休的渔船船主 这是我侄女。
Yup. I'm Aivan, I'm 32 years old,
是的。 我是艾万, 我32岁了,
and I'm a general contractor.
我是总承包商。
All right, who we have over here?
没事, 我们在这里是谁?
My name is Shanda and this is my cousin Asa,
我叫Shanda 这是我表弟阿萨,
and we come from a family of chefs.
我们来自 厨师的家庭。
- Wow. So they run restaurants? - Well, so, my dad,
- 哇。 他们经营餐馆吗? 好吧,所以,我爸爸,
he was a chef for 35 years, and trained his brothers,
他是一位35年的厨师, 训练他的弟兄,
- who were also chefs. - Very nice.
他们也是厨师。 - 非常漂亮。
All right, if you want an apron, now's the time to step up.
如果你想要一条围裙, 现在是加紧的时候了。
- Are you ready? - We're ready!
你准备好了吗? 我们准备好了!
All right, let's see who's the best! Your time starts now!
好的, 让我们看看谁是最好的! 你的时间现在开始!
- Thank you. - Yes!
- 谢谢。 - 是的!
- Gordon: Let's go! - Tina: Let's go Aivan.
戈登:我们走吧! 蒂娜:我们去艾凡。
- I'm coming, I'm coming. - Let's cook.
我来了,我来了。 让我们做饭。
- This is gonna be an exciting battle. - Yeah!
This is gonna be 的 激动人心的战斗。 是的!
- Shanda, you need anything? - I'm good, baby.
山达,你需要什么吗? 我很好,宝贝。
- Let's go. - Extended family.
我们走吧。 - 大家庭。
Sometimes that can get a little complicated.
有时,这可以得到 有点复杂。
But in the kitchen? Man, it's just fireworks, right?
在厨房? 人,这只是烟花,对吧?
I didn't really cook a whole lot with my family.
我真的没有做饭 和我的家人在一起。
- We kind of cooked separate and brought things together. - Sure.
我们有点煮熟了 并将事物聚集在一起。 - 当然。
But then when we would get in the kitchen, there was a lot of, like,
但后来当 我们进入厨房, 有很多,就像,
"No, no, no. You don't make it this way, you make it that way."
“不,不,不。 你不这样, 你这样做 。 "
- Careful with the knife, baby. - Will do.
小心刀子,宝贝。 威尔·威尔。
Aivan and Tina, give us an insight into the dish you're making.
艾文和蒂娜, 给我们一个洞察 你做菜。
- We're making my grandma's steamed bass with-- - Steamed?
We're making my grandma's 我们做奶奶的 蒸馅的低音与—— 蒸?
- You need to speak up, honey. - Oh.
你需要说话,亲爱的。 - 哦。
- We cannot hear nothing from you. - Can you hear me over there?
我们听不到 没有什么从你。 你能听到我那边吗?
She's got the big mouth, not me.
她有大嘴巴, 而不是我。
We're making steamed bass with glass noodles
我们正在制作蒸馅的低音 玻璃面条
- and black bean sauce. - Gordon: Love that.
黑豆酱。 戈登:爱这个。
- Whereabouts is grandma from? - From Vietnam.
奶奶从哪里来? 来自越南。
In 1975, she immigrated to the United States with my aunt, uncle, and my mom.
1975年,她移民到 美国与我的姑姑, 叔叔,还有我妈妈。
So being here and representing her and sharing our culture
所以在这里和代表 她和分享我们的文化
- and heritage is crazy. It's so special. - I love that.
遗产是疯狂的。 太特别了。 我喜欢这个。
Brilliant. And, Tina, now that you've retired,
灿烂。 而且,蒂娜, 现在你已经退休了,
- are you spending more time in the kitchen cooking? - Tina: Yes.
你花更多的时间吗? 在厨房做饭? 蒂娜:是的。
I spend a lot of time in my kitchen.
我花了很多时间 在我的厨房里。
Aivan: All day every day.
艾文: 每一天。
Tina: If you tell me to go cook, I mean, I glow.
蒂娜: 如果你叫我去做饭, 我是说,我发光。
If you tell me to go do laundry,
如果你叫我去洗衣服,
no, that can wait till tomorrow.
不能等到明天。
- You're funny, by the way. - She is the life of the party.
你很有趣,顺便说一句。 她是党的生活。
- I bet. - Whoo!
我打赌。 - Whoo!
- Toasting. - Pistachios?
- 烤。 - 开心果?
- Yep. Throw them in. - I got you.
- 是的。 把它们扔进去。 我得到了你。
B-b-b-b-- that's it. Yeah!
B-b-b-B - 就是这样。 是的!
Shanda and Asa, what are you preparing for us this evening?
Shanda 和 Asa,你是什么 今晚为我们做准备?
We have a pistachio risotto with duck breast
我们有一个开心果里斯托 鸭胸
We have four uncles that are chefs.
我们有四个叔叔。 那就是厨师。
This is their spin on the classic risotto.
这是他们的旋转 在经典的里斯托。
And I think it's important to note, Chef,
而我认为 重要的是要注意,厨师,
that our uncles, they weren't classically trained,
我们的叔叔,他们不是 受过古典训练,
but they learned on the job, and they were trained by chefs
但他们在工作中学到了, 他们接受了厨师的训练。
from France and northern Italy.
法国和意大利北部。
Working with great chefs
与伟大的厨师合作
is really the road to becoming a great chef.
真的是路 成为一个伟大的厨师。
100%. We're from a huge family.
100%。 我们来自一个大家庭。
- Joe: Got it. - Cooking is our rite of passage.
乔:得了。 烹饪是我们的仪式 通道。
So you're doubling down on the jeopardy,
所以你加倍了 在危险中,
because you're making risotto, which is very difficult enough.
因为你做Risotto, 这已经够难的了。
Then you're gonna render and sear a duck breast.
然后你会渲染 和海烙鸭胸。
That's a tall order in 30 minutes.
这是一个很高的命令 在30分钟内。
Well, we have a lot of confidence in ourselves, chef.
好吧,我们有很多 自信自己,厨师。
And I believe that we'll be able to get this done for you.
我相信我们会能够的 为你完成这件事。
Tiffany: All right, we're looking forward to it.
蒂芙尼:好的, 我们期待它。
So we're 20 minutes down. We have 10 minutes remaining.
所以我们是20分钟。 我们还有10分钟。
- Let's go. - Fish is in.
我们走吧。 鱼在。
With that Vietnamese steamed bass,
与那个越南人 蒸馍低音,
the cooking on the bass it is very hard because it's thick and dense.
低音上的烹饪 非常困难,因为 它又厚又密。
But if they can pull that off, then that could be a great dish.
但是,如果他们能把它拉下来, 这可能是一道很棒的菜。
- Gordon: Yeah. - It's good.
戈登:是的。 - 很好。
- Aivan: Okay. - How's the duck ducking?
艾文:好的。 鸭子躲闪怎么样?
- He ducking. - ( Shanda laughs )
他躲开了。 (Shanda Laughs)
So Shanda and Asa are taking two of the most difficult things
所以 Shanda 和 Asa 正在服用 最困难的两件事
that we see throughout the years here and putting them on one plate?
我们看到的整个 岁月在这里和放 他们在一个盘子吗?
I mean, how do you make risotto within 30 minutes?
我是说, 你如何制作Risotto 30分钟内?
- That's tough. - Yeah.
这很难。 - 是的。
Behind you. Behind you.
你身后。 你身后。
Right, how are we doing with this risotto?
对,我们怎么样 这个Risotto?
Shanda: It's coming along. It's coming along.
尚达:来了。 来了。
How have you got the pistachios in the risotto?
你怎么得到开心果 在里斯托?
- What have you done? - I chopped them down
你做了什么? 我把它们砍下来
and then I used a little butter. How's that?
然后我用一点黄油。 怎么样?
So you need a touch more stock in there
所以你需要触摸 更多的库存
so the kernels can bloom and absorb that.
所以 kernels 可以绽放和吸收它。
- Thank you, Chef. - Okay, 'cause it's just a little bit undercooked.
谢谢你,厨师。 好的,因为这只是 有点不熟。
- Okay. Will do. - Make sure that rice is cooked.
- 好的。 会做的。 确保米饭煮熟。
Keep tasting. Six minutes to go guys. Yes?
继续品尝。 六分钟去伙计们。 是的?
- Okay. Thank you. - You want to check it?
- 好的。 谢谢你。 你想检查它吗?
- Just look at it real quick. - Excellent.
看着它真的很快。 - 优秀。
- You can turn it off. Mm. Smells good. - Okay.
你可以关掉它。 姆。 闻起来很好。 - 好的。
Five minutes remaining. Let's go!
剩下五分钟。 我们走吧!
- Shanda: Oh, boy. - Asa: Talk to me, Shanda. What you got?
- 尚达:哦,男孩。 阿萨:跟我说话,山达。 你得到了什么?
I don't want to lift the lid anymore. I want it to cook.
我不想要 揭开盖子。 我想让它做饭。
Shanda and Asa, they've reduced the stock so much, it wasn't absorbing.
Shanda 和 Asa ,他们已经减少了 股票这么多, 它不是吸收的。
So the rice wasn't blooming, and so it is dry.
所以米饭没有开花, 所以它是干燥的。
It needs more liquid.
它需要更多的液体。
Gordon: If they don't fix this fast,
戈登: 如果他们不快速修复,
they're gonna run out of time.
他们会耗尽时间。
( groans )
(呻吟)
I don't want to lift the lid anymore. I want it to cook.
我不想举起 盖子了。 我想让它做饭。
How much more time do you have left on your risotto?
多少时间你 离开你的Risotto了吗?
- About three minutes. - Hurry up and wait, baby. Hurry up and wait.
大约三分钟。 快点等,宝贝。 快点,等待。
- That's right. - Okay, I'm gonna take the fish,
- 没错。 好吧,我要把鱼,
and then you're gonna season the noodles a little bit for me.
然后你会季节 面条对我来说有点。
Final two minutes.
最后两分钟。
Start thinking about the plating.
开始思考 关于电镀。
How you feeling on that risotto?
你对那个里斯托的感觉如何?
All right, I'm ready to go. Let's start plating, baby.
好了,我准备好了。 让我们开始镀层吧,宝贝。
- Come on! Finishing touches. Let's go! - Ooh, look at that.
来吧! 完成触摸。 我们走吧! 哦,看看这个。
- Come on, come on, come on. - We got it. We got it.
来吧,来吧,来吧,来吧。 我们得到了它。 我们得到了。
Five, four, three, two, one.
五,四,三,二,一。
- Gordon: And stop. Hands in the air. - Joe: Hands up.
戈登:然后停下来。 手在空中。 乔:举起手来。
- Well done. - Good job!
- 干得好。 干得好!
Joe: All right.
乔:对。
So, first up Aivan and Tina, please bring us your dish.
所以,首先,艾凡和蒂娜, 请把你的菜带给我们。
Aivan: We made my grandma's steamed bass
艾凡:我们做的 我奶奶的蒸馍低音
with black bean sauce, glass noodles, and herb salad.
黑豆酱, 玻璃面条和草药沙拉。
I love the elegance of this.
我喜欢这个的优雅。
I'm dying to taste it because it's got "eat me" all over it.
我渴望品尝它 因为它有“吃我” 都越过它。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
It's glistening.
闪闪发光。
Fish is cooked beautifully.
鱼煮得很漂亮。
And what you've done with that ginger, it's delicious.
And you've done with 你做了什么 姜,很好吃。
- Thank you. - Thank you, Chef.
- 谢谢。 谢谢你,大厨。
The noodles itself are perfect.
面条本身是完美的。
I will say though, I wish that it had a little acid.
我会说,我希望 它有一点酸。
Whether that's just a zest of the lime to kind of perk it up...
是否如此 只是一个热情的石灰 为了把它举起来......
- Yes. - Tasting this dish
- 是的。 - 品尝这道菜
is like coming to your house for dinner.
喜欢来 去你家吃晚饭。
Full flavor, delicious. Good job.
味道全,美味。 好工作。
Welcome to my home. My door always open for you, Joe.
欢迎来到我的家。 我的门总是 为你敞开,乔。
- Excellent. - Okay, Joe!
- 优秀。 好吧,乔!
- Thank you. - Thank you very, very much.
- 谢谢。 非常感谢,非常。
The freshness of that, that was lovely. I love the idea of the lime.
新鲜, 那是可爱的。 我喜欢石灰的想法。
All right, Shanda, Asa, please bring us your dish.
没事,Shanda,Ana, 请把你的菜带给我们。
Shanda: We present to you a pan seared duck with a pistachio risotto.
尚达:我们向你介绍 泛 烫鸭 开心果Risotto。
It's a dish that's very inviting.
是一道菜 这是非常诱人的。
There's a lot of technique that you put into this.
有很多技术 你投入这个。
You're really doing two dishes in one
你真的在做 在两个盘子在一个
because a risotto would have been enough on its own.
因为一个risotto会 已经够自己了。
- So I'm very eager to try it. - Thank you, chef.
所以我非常渴望尝试。 谢谢你,厨师。
Shall we?
我们要?
The duck is juicy. It's seasoned beautifully.
鸭子多汁。 很美。
But then you've got the richness of that risotto.
但是你得到了 丰富那利斯托。
It's a little bit too rich and too heavy.
有点太有钱了 而且太重了。
And the consistency, it's not giving the true risotto texture, but it's delicious.
一致性,它不是 给出真正的Risotto纹理, 很好吃。
- Okay. Thank you. - Yes, Chef.
- 好的。 谢谢你。 是的,大厨。
The duck is beautiful.
鸭子很漂亮。
So much flavor. Really well-seasoned.
这么多风味。 真的很有味道。
You've allowed it to rest.
你允许它休息。
You've done all the right steps
你已经做了所有正确的步骤
to make the duck delicious.
使鸭子美味。
- Thank you, Chef. - Look, the flavor is very rich and intense.
谢谢你,大厨。 看,味道是 非常丰富和强烈。
But the risotto was undercooked.
但是里斯托被煮熟了。
- Thank you both. - Both: Thank you.
谢谢两位。 两位:谢谢。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Good job.
好工作。
Hold me tight.
紧紧的抱着我。
Okay, the best dish in this battle was cooked by...
好的,最好的菜 在这场战斗中,被...
Tina and Aivan!
蒂娜和艾凡!
- What? - Congratulations.
- 什么? - 恭喜。
- Run, run! - Thank you, Gordon.
跑,跑! 谢谢你,戈登。
- Congratulations. - Thank you so much.
恭喜。 谢谢你这么多。
- Thank you so much. - Thank you, Gordon.
谢谢你这么多。 谢谢你,戈登。
- Well done. - Tiffany: Shanda, Asa, you should be really proud.
- 干得好。 - 蒂芙尼:尚达、阿萨、 你应该真的感到骄傲。
The the dish that you created had lots of flavor.
你创造的菜 有很多味道。
Do not let this keep you down.
不要让这让你失望。
- Thank you. - This was awesome.
谢谢你。 这太棒了。
Asa: Very disappointing.
阿萨:非常令人失望。
It may not have been what the judges wanted.
可能不是 法官想要的。
There's a lot of things that we can improve on.
有很多事情 我们可以改进。
And we'll take everything that they said to heart.
And we'll take everything 我们会拿走一切 他们心里说。
- ( screaming ) - Look what we got!
( scream) 看看我们得到了什么!
Brought us some good luck.
给我们带来了一些好运。
This is even better than my wedding dress. Trust me.
这甚至比 我的婚纱 相信我。
I'm gonna wear this to the day I die.
我要穿这个 到我死去的那一天。
( squealing, cheering )
(吱吱声,欢呼)
- Next up, Timothy and Athena... - ( gasping )
下一步, 蒂莫西和雅典娜 - 喘气
- ...versus Azu and Javier. - Aah!
. . . 相对于阿祖和哈维尔。 - 啊!
Azu: We came here to win.
阿祖: 我们来这里是为了赢。
If I don't get that apron,
如果我没有得到那个围裙,
I'm gonna stop talking to him for the rest of my life.
我要停止和他说话 我的余生。
- Please, God. - But we're gonna get it. I mean, it's for sure.
拜托,上帝。 但是我们会得到它。 我的意思是,这是肯定的。
- Oh, my God. - Look at these!
哦,我的上帝。 看看这些!
This competition is fierce. It's cutthroat.
这种竞争非常激烈。 是喉凰。
We know it's gonna be tough, but winning that prize money
我们知道这将是艰难的, 但赢得这个奖金
would change our lives tremendously.
改变我们的生活 巨大的。
- It's about to be us right there. - Yeah?
曲名 : It's to be 我们就在那里。 是啊?
We're coming to win that battle first,
我们来赢 这场战斗第一,
- get that apron, and win the rest of the competition. - 100%.
得到那个围裙,然后赢 其余的竞争。 - 100%。
Holy guacamole, baby!
神圣的瓜卡莫尔,宝贝!
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. I'm going to faint.
哦,我的上帝。 哦,我的上帝。 我要晕倒了。
( squealing )
(吱吱声)
This is real. Oh, my God.
这是真实的。 哦,我的上帝。
Good evening to all four of you.
晚安 给你四个人。
- Thank you, Chefs. - Thank you.
谢谢你,厨师。 - 谢谢。
- To my left, please introduce yourselves. - My name is Timothy.
在我的左边, 请介绍一下自己。 我叫Timothy。
This is my beautiful wife Athena.
这是我的美丽 妻子雅典娜。
We just got married and this is our honeymoon.
我们刚结婚 这是我们的蜜月。
- Congratulations! - Thank you very much.
恭喜! 非常感谢你。
- Hope it's worth it! - It's definitely worth it.
希望值得! 绝对值得。
- Definitely worth it. - And where did you propose?
绝对值得。 你在哪里求婚的?
I proposed in Huntington Beach in California.
我提议 亨廷顿海滩 在加州。
I told her to face the ocean and put her hands up
我告诉她要面对海洋。 举起双手
And I turned around, and I was like, "Baby, what are you--"
而我转身, 我就像, “宝贝,你是什么——”
- He was on one knee. - That is amazing.
他单膝跪地。 这太神奇了。
All right, who we have over here?
没事, 我们在这里是谁?
- My name is Azucena. - My name is Javier.
我叫Azucena。 我叫哈维尔。
We have been divorced 14 years.
我们离婚了14年。
We're ex-couples, but we have two things in common.
我们是前夫妇,但我们有 共同点的两件事
One is food, and our son Santiago, the love of our lives.
一个是食物, 我们的儿子圣地亚哥, 我们生命中的爱
Since we divorced, we decided that we were gonna remain friends forever
自从我们离婚了, 我们决定,我们是 永远 永远 保持 朋友
for the well-being of our son.
为我们儿子的福祉。
And it's a promise that we made,
这是一个承诺,我们
and thanks to that promise, we can be here today.
感谢这个承诺, 我们今天可以在这里。
You want to remember why you got divorced? Is that why you're here?
你想记住 你为什么离婚? 这就是为什么你在这里吗?
- ( laughing ) - Joe: So now--
(笑) 乔:现在——
- I mean, I like Javier very much. - Okay.
我是说,我喜欢 哈维尔非常。 - 好的。
I know he can get on my nerves, but--
我知道他可以上 我的神经,但是——
and I can get particularly on his nerves.
我可以特别得到 在他的神经。
You two, put your fingers in your ears now.
这两个人,把你的手指 现在在你的耳朵里。
Oh, my God. I'm so sorry.
哦,我的上帝。 对不起。
Joe: Newlyweds and divorced.
乔: 新婚夫妇和离婚。
- The two opposite ends of the extreme. - Yes, sir.
- 两条相反的末端 的极端。 “是的,先生。
- Absolutely. - Listen, if you want to earn your white aprons,
- 绝对。 听着,如果你想赚钱 你的白色围裙,
we'd love to see food that really reflects your bond.
我们喜欢看食物 这真的反映了你的债券。
Get it on the plate, but put it on with love. Understood?
把它放在盘子里, 穿上爱。 理解?
- Yes! - Your time starts now!
- 是的! 你的时间现在开始!
- Let's go! - Oh, my God!
我们走吧! 哦,我的上帝!
- This way. This way. - Okay, this'll be fascinating.
- 这种方式。 这种方式。 好吧,这将是迷人的。
- Yeah, it is. - And with only one duo going through,
是的,是的。 只有一个二人组 走过,
it's definitely gonna end in heartbreak.
它肯定会结束 在心碎。
I cannot be nervous, but I'm a little nervous.
我不能紧张, 但我有点紧张。
- You okay? - Yeah, I'm good.
你没事吧? 是的,我很好。
So you have the newlyweds that are spending
所以你有新婚夫妇 那就是支出
- all their time together. - Yes.
他们在一起的时间。 - 是的。
You have the divorced couple
你有离婚的夫妇
who have been separated for 14 years.
被分开的人 14年。
Obviously have a history of cooking together.
显然有历史 一起做饭。
- Who's got the advantage? - Hmm. It's a tough one.
谁有优势? - 哼。 这是个艰难的时期。
- I'd say the history. - I agree.
我会说历史。 我同意。
- I don't know. - No?
我不知道。 - 不?
I think the fact that they've been doing it,
我认为事实 他们一直在这样做,
they're in rhythm right now.
他们现在处于节奏之中。
History over here might repeat itself.
历史在这里 可能会重复自己。
- True. - Oh, baby.
- 真的。 哦,宝贝。
- Yeah? I'm getting the potato started. - Hell, yeah.
是啊? 我得到了 土豆开始了。 地狱,是的。
Timothy, Athena, what are y'all making?
蒂莫西,雅典娜, 都在制造什么?
we are making a rack of curried lamb,
我们正在制作一个机架 咖喱羊羔,
some creamy mashed potatoes, and sweet asparagus.
一些奶油土豆泥, 甜芦笋。
Give me insight in to the curry.
给我洞察力 腋在咖喱里。
My wife is a curry queen.
我的妻子是咖喱女王。
She's making the curry paste right now.
她在制造 咖喱膏现在。
- In a half hour? - Yes, sir.
半小时后? “是的,先生。
- Oh, absolutely. - Gordon: Wow.
哦,绝对的。 戈登:哇。
- You curry in a hurry. - Curry in a hurry.
你匆忙地咖喱。 咖喱在匆忙中。
- That's how we do. - These for you, right here.
我们就是这样做的。 这些给你,就在这里。
- Okay, thank you so much. - Azu, Javier.
好的,非常感谢你。 - 阿祖,哈维尔。
- Yes, Chef? - What are y'all making?
是的,大厨? 各位在制造什么?
- Chicken roulade stew. - This is a chicken breast
- 鸡肉胭脂炖菜。 这是一只鸡胸肉
with almonds and raisins...
杏仁和葡萄干...
...that we prepare in weddings and funerals.
我们准备的 在婚礼和葬礼上。
I have to say, considering your complicated situation,
不得不说,考虑 你的复杂情况,
the irony is not lost on us.
讽刺并没有迷失在我们身上。
So it's the marriage and death dish.
所以是婚姻 死亡碟。
Well, I think that you're gonna like it, chef.
嗯,我想 你会喜欢的,厨师。
Guys, we're coming up to halfway. 15 minutes gone.
伙计们,我们来了 到一半。 15分钟过去了。
- Ay, yi, yi. - 15 minutes to go.
- Ay, yi, yi。 15分钟就走了。
- ( speaking Spanish ) - Right.
- (说西班牙语) - 正确。
- ( speaking Spanish ) - Ah.
- (说西班牙语) - 啊。
Chef, don't get too close. I don't want your jacket to get stained.
厨师,不要太靠近。 我不想要你的夹克 去沾染。
No, it's all good. Tell me about this sauce.
不,一切都好。 说说这个酱汁。
I want a texture that is similar to like a "molito."
我想要一个纹理 类似于“molito”。
- Yes. What's in there? - I'm working on it.
- 是的。 那里有什么? 我在努力。
- No, Chef! No, Chef! One minute please! - Mmm.
不,大厨! 不,大厨! 一分钟,请! - 嗯。
Gordon: And what's your sous chef doing?
戈登: 你的厨师在做什么?
The sous chef is doing the chicken.
厨师 做鸡。
- Okay, good. Where is the chicken? - It's the oven right now.
好的,好的。 鸡在哪里? 现在是烤箱。
Right. Just over 10 minutes to go.
对了。 只需10分钟。
- Oh, my God. I'm getting nervous. - Lots of time.
哦,我的上帝。 我很紧张。 - 大量时间。
You're fine. Talk to each other.
你很好。 互相交谈。
Timothy and Athena.
蒂莫西和雅典娜。
- Yes, sir. Yes, sir. - Hello, hello.
“是的,先生。 是的,先生。 你好,你好。
In love. Is Athena your goddess?
在爱情中。 雅典娜是你的女神吗?
- Yes, she is. - Athena is the goddess of what?
是的,她是。 雅典娜是女神 什么?
- Wisdom and war. I'm here to fight. - Oh!
智慧与战争 我是来战斗的。 - 哦!
- Yes, ma'am. - Love it.
是的,太太。 爱它。
Tiffany: It looks really good, y'all.
蒂芙尼: 看起来真的很好,你们。
- And make sure you season everything. - Yes, chef.
- 并确保 你季节的一切。 是的,厨师。
Mm. Mm! Mm!
姆。 咪! 咪!
- 25 gone. - Oh, my gosh.
25 走了 哦,天哪。
Gordon: We're down to our last five minutes.
戈登:我们倒下了 最后五分钟。
Azu and Javier, it's funny
阿祖和哈维尔,真有意思
because they're not talking as much. I thought they would--
因为他们 说话不多。 我以为他们会——
- Oh, my goodness. - But she's making an amazing
哦,我的天哪。 她正在做一个惊人的
sauce with those almonds, tomatoes, and the raisins,
酱汁与那些杏仁, 西红柿和葡萄干,
- and it tastes delicious. - How we looking on the curry?
味道很好吃。 我们如何看待咖喱?
- Salt. - Little bit?
- 盐。 一点点?
- Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah. - Gordon: It smells good.
哦,是的。 是的,是的。 戈登:味道不错。
What do we smell? The curry though?
我们闻到了什么味道? 咖喱?
Definitely smell the curry...
绝对闻到咖喱的味道......
- Tiffany: Yeah. - ( speaking Spanish )
蒂芙尼:是的。 - (说西班牙语)
- This has to be right. - What's he doing now?
这必须是正确的。 他现在在做什么?
Is he gonna cook it twice?
他要煮两次吗?
Oh, no. He's cutting it and cooking it again?
哦,不。 他在剪它 再煮一次?
Joe: I think that's a panic move.
乔: 我认为那是恐慌的举动。
That probably wasn't their original plan.
那可能不是 他们原来的计划。
And at this point, if he's second-guessing
而此时, 如果他是第二次猜测
and gonna sear it in the pan,
并让它在锅里,
there's a definite chance it's gonna come out dry.
有一定的机会 它会干的。
- Yeah. - That might cost them
- 是的。 这可能使他们付出代价
some real flavor points.
一些真正的风味点。
I'm not too sure if Javier has got this.
我不太确定 如果哈维尔有这个。
He seems a little bit distant right now.
他似乎有点 遥远的现在。
- Yeah. - Is there an argument going on there?
- 是的。 - 有争论吗 去那里吗?
( speaking Spanish )
(说西班牙语)
Don't overcook the chicken, guys.
不要煮过 鸡,伙计们。
- Javier: Totally fine. - No, no. Not totally fine.
哈维尔:完全没了。 不,不。 不完全好。
Not for me. No, no, no, no, no.
不是我。 不,不,不,不,不。
No, no.
不,不。
We are coming down to our final 60 seconds.
我们下来了 最后60秒
One minute to go. Start plating. Come on.
一分钟就走了。 开始拼盘。 来吧。
- Lamb, babe. - Let's go!
羔羊,宝贝。 我们走吧!
( speaking Spanish )
(说西班牙语)
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six,
十,九, 八,七,六,
five, four, three, two, one.
五,四,三,二,一。
- And stop. Well done. - Hands up.
停止。 干得好。 举起手。
- Joe: All right. - Gordon: Well done.
乔:好的。 戈登:干得好。
All right, Timothy and Athena,
蒂莫西和雅典娜,
please bring us your dish.
请把你的菜带给我们。
Timothy: We made curried lamb chops, creamy mashed potatoes,
蒂莫西: 我们做了咖喱羊排, 奶油土豆泥,
candied asparagus, and a mint chutney.
芦笋 一个薄荷榻米。
- Visually, it looks good. - Thank you very much.
视觉上,看起来不错。 非常感谢你。
So the rack of lamb needs to be pink right?
羊羔的架子 应该是粉红色的对吗?
- Yes, sir. - Gordon: And...
“是的,先生。 戈登:而且......
Mmm! Wow!
嗯! 哇!
Gordon: Absolutely beautiful.
戈登: 绝对漂亮。
Been waiting to hear those words from you, Chef.
一直等待听到 这些话来自你,厨师。
( squeals )
(吱吱声)
Lamb is cooked beautifully.
羊羔煮得很漂亮。
It's quite a rare technique there,
相当罕见 技术在那里,
to cook the lamb that perfectly
煮羔羊,完美的
and coat it in a curry sauce.
把它涂在咖喱酱里。
That is a marriage made in heaven.
那是一段婚姻 在天堂制造。
That's harmony right there.
那里是和谐的。
The finesse comes from her.
技巧来自她。
She's taught me everything I know.
她教过我 我所知道的一切。
Definitely newlyweds here.
绝对是新婚夫妇在这里。
I mean, look at this. It's very rare that people
我是说,看看这个。 非常罕见的是,人们
can cook a rack of lamb that perfectly.
能煮一架羊肉 完美。
Asparagus itself is sort of where I feel like the plate is lacking.
芦笋本身 有点像我觉得喜欢的地方 盘子是缺乏的。
I know you said sweet asparagus, but I'm not getting the sweetness there.
我知道你说过甜芦笋, I'm not getting 我没有得到 那里的甜蜜。
- But you got the meat down. - Thank you, Chef.
但是你把肉弄下来了。 谢谢你,大厨。
You know, I think that this dish really represents the unity
你知道,我想这道菜 真正代表团结
and the love that you guys share right now.
和 爱情 , 你 们 分享现在。
- Wow! Joe! - Joe!
哇! 乔! 乔!
You may kiss the bride.
你可以亲吻新娘。
- Thank you. - Good job, guys.
- 谢谢。 工作很好,伙计们。
Azu, Javier, bring your plate forward please.
阿祖,哈维尔,带上你的盘子 向前请。
Oh. What's going on?
哦。 这是怎么回事?
This is just to bring a little bit of the aroma of the cinnamon.
只是为了带来 一点点香气 肉桂
Javier: The dish we have made today is a chicken roulade stew.
哈维尔: 我们今天做的菜 是鸡莺炖菜。
Azu: Which is a chicken breast with almonds and raisins, sauce from Oaxaca.
阿祖:这是鸡胸肉 杏仁和葡萄干, 来自瓦哈卡的酱汁。
Visually, listen, it's attractive.
视觉上,听着, 很有吸引力。
Now I've been to Oaxaca, but I've never seen a stew that firm.
现在我去过瓦哈卡, 但我从来没有看过 炖这家公司。
- Was that the intention? - Yes.
这是意图吗? - 是的。
We decided to make it a little bit more condensed.
我们决定让它 稍微凝结一点。
Gordon: Let's taste it, shall we?
戈登: 让我们品尝一下,我们会吗?
First off, the chicken's cooked beautifully.
首先,鸡的 煮得很漂亮。
It's seasoned well. The sauce is delicious.
很有经验的。 酱汁很好吃。
But I would have preferred it to be a little bit more liquid.
但我宁愿它 多一点液体。
Just a little bit more relaxed.
只是稍微放松一点。
Overall, I think the flavors are really nice.
总体而言, 我认为口味 真的很好。
The sweetness with the saltiness of the plantains
甜蜜与 芭蕉的咸味
works together really, really well.
一起努力,真的 真的好。
And, Javi, the chicken itself is beautifully cooked.
而且,贾维,鸡本身 煮得很漂亮。
I was very concerned because I saw it go back in the pan.
我非常担心,因为 我看见它回到了锅里。
I'm like, "Oh, my God. It's chicken breast.
我就像,"哦,我的上帝。 是鸡胸肉。
There's no skin. There's no fat."
没有皮肤。 没有脂肪 。 ”
But you did a really good job
但是你做了很好的工作
of making sure that that was done right.
确保这一点 这是正确的。
- Thank you, Chef. - Thank you, Chef.
谢谢你,厨师。 谢谢你,厨师。
The dish actually comes together and eats really, really well.
这道菜实际上在一起了 吃真的,真的很好。
An excellent effort. For two people who have been separated to come together
出色的努力。 对于两个去过的人 分开走到一起
and to create something like this is really quite an accomplishment.
并创造一些东西 像这样真的是 相当的成就。
- Azu: Thank you so much. - Thank you, Chef.
阿祖:非常感谢。 谢谢你,大厨。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Please give us a moment.
请给我们一点时间。
When we get that apron.
当我们得到那个围裙。
- Are we in agreeance? Yeah? - Yeah.
我们同意吗? 是啊? 是啊。
Hmm.
哼。
Okay, we felt the best dish
好吧,我们觉得最好的菜
in this battle was cooked by...
在这场战斗中,由...
Okay, we felt the best dish
好吧,我们觉得最好的菜
in this battle was cooked by...
在这场战斗中,由...
Timothy and Athena.
蒂莫西和雅典娜。
It looks like the honeymoon's gonna have to wait
看起来像蜜月。 将不得不等待
a little bit longer, guys. Way to go!
稍微长一点,伙计们。 要走的路!
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you so much.
谢谢你。 谢谢你。 非常感谢你。
- Oh, here you go. - Thank you.
哦,你走吧。 - 谢谢。
Gordon: Azu, Javier, there's something quite dynamic about you two
戈登: 阿祖,哈维尔,有事 关于你两个的动态
and the passion you bring to the kitchen. That's obvious.
以及你带来的激情 到厨房。 这是显而易见的。
Such a shame, because the chicken was delicious,
这样的耻辱,因为 鸡是美味的,
but the dish, it was just a little bit too stiff.
但菜,它只是 有点太僵硬了。
- But thank you. - Thank you.
谢谢你。 谢谢你。
Azu: I'm sad, of course, but listen.
阿祖:我很难过, 当然,但听。
It has been a great experience to share with Javier these days.
这是一次很棒的经历 这些天要和哈维尔分享。
For me, it's already a great gift.
对我来说,它已经 很棒的礼物。
And it just didn't happen, but it's okay.
它只是没有发生, 但没事。
- ( cheering ) - Aah!
- (欢呼) 啊!
- Oh, my God! - Yeah!
哦,我的上帝! 是啊!
This has been an amazing year. We just got married.
这是惊人的一年。 我们刚刚结婚。
We marked that off. MasterChef apron?
我们标记了。 MasterChef apron ?
- Both: Marked that off. - Next thing is the trophy.
两者:标记它。 接下来就是奖杯。
Whoo!
寯寯!
So, that's three sets of aprons down, five remaining.
所以,这是三套围裙 下来,剩下的五个。
And honestly, so far, I am so impressed.
老实说,到目前为止, 我印象深刻。
Next time on "MasterChef: Dynamic Duos"...
下次在 《MasterChef: Dynamic Duos》
Welcome, welcome, welcome.
欢迎,欢迎,欢迎。
- the audition battles continue... - Let's go!
试镜战斗 继续...... 我们走吧!
as more home cook duos go head-to-head...
更多家庭厨师二人组 去头对头......
Come on, Ash! Let's do it.
来吧,Ash! 让我们去做吧。
- We want that white apron. - Nice flambe.
我们想要那个白色的围裙。 - 漂亮的火焰。
We're here to win. We're taking 'em down.
我们在这里是为了赢。 我们正在把“他们”拿下来。
...to try to secure a pair of coveted white aprons.
尝试确保一对 令人垂涎的白色围裙
You guys know how to make a fire, right?
你们都知道 如何制造火灾,对吧?
- You're about to get extinguished. - Rawr!
你即将得到 熄灭。 Rawr!
We really see the dynamic duo in the dish.
我们真的看到了动态的二人组 在盘子里。
And you're going to give us an apron for it.
和你要给我们 围裙。
- It's a little messy. - Joe: You really shot for the stars.
- 有点乱。 乔:你真的开枪了 对于星星。
- Here we go. - And you just missed.
我们走。 你只是错过了。
- Oh, boy. - Oh, my God.
哦,男孩。 哦,我的上帝。